

# Alona Kuznietsova

# Junior Frontend Developer

I am a Frontend Developer with expertise in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React. I am proficient in SASS, BEM, Tailwind CSS, and Emotion-styles. I specialize in creating adaptive layouts and using adaptive graphics. I have experience as a Team Leader and Scrum Master in team projects. I excel at researching and utilizing information from diverse sources, quickly learning new tasks, and adapting to new software. I possess an analytical mindset and have extensive experience in remote work.

+49-15141896120

github.com/acvetochka

acvetochka@gmail.com

Q +380-961270693

© Erkheim, Germany

in linkedin.com/in/alona-kuznietsova

# **Tech Skills**

- HTML5
- CSS3/SASS
- Adaptive design
- A11y
- GIT/Github
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- REST API
- JSON/Yaml

- Axios
- WebPack
- Parcel
- React
- Redux
- Redux Toolkit
- Node.js
- Next.is
- MongoDB
- Express.js
- Markdown
- Swagger

# React-App

**Projects** 

O Portfolio - Github

SmileBar - Github

Car Rental - Github

Carp Travel - Github

React-App on the Next.js

Car-rental website. On the site, the possibility of filtering cars and adding them to favorites has been implemented. The project used Emotion-styled

Website is a business card offering active recreation in the Carpathians. Features: Responsive Design, Swiper Integration. The project used Tailwind CSS,

Personal portfolio website. Includes personal information, skills, work experience, certificates, and projects. Provides fast navigation and a responsive

Responsive, cross-browser website for a professional dental cleaning studio in

Technologies: React JS, Redux Toolkit, Axios

design for a seamless viewing experience on any device.

Commercial team project by SoftRyzen. Role: Developer

Lviv. It uses the Sanity administrative panel and Telegram chat bot.

Technologies: Next JS, Tailwind CSS, Sanity, Telegram bot API

Technologies: Next JS, TypeScript, Vercel

### **Education**

#### Master of Telecommunication

Odesa National Academy of Telecommunications O.S. Popov 09/2006 - 06/2010 | Ukraine

#### Master of Law

**European University** 09/2020 - 12.2021 | Ukraine

# Technologies: React JS, Next.js, Vercel

**Goose Track** - **Github** 

React Hook Form

Team-project. Role: Frontend Team Lead, Scrum Master, Developer.

Event calendar management application! The project has Google-authorization. Stylized using Emotion-styled

Technologies: React JS, Redux Toolkit, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB

# Certificates

- Telc DTB B2 07/2024
- VueJS 06/2024
- DevOps and Kubernetes 05/2024
- Digital Marketing and e-Commerce -Google - 03/2024
- TypeScript 03/2024
- Englisch B1 12/2023
- FullStack Developer 10/2023

# Phonebook - Github

React-App for storing contacts with authorization. The project used Emotion-

Technologies: React JS, Redux Toolkit, Axios

#### **Booksheft - Github**

Team-project. Role: Developer.

A platform for searching and buying books. Website with a responsive layout. App component with Public and Private routes, AuthPage page logic.

Technologies: HTML, SASS, JS, Parcel, Rest API, Firebase

#### Mimino - Github

Team-project. Role: Team-lead, developer.

Website of the hotel and restaurant complex. Adaptive layout and adaptive graphics were implemented. Build project on github, check for build errors and live page performance.

Technologies: HTML, SASS, JS, Parcel

# Languages

• English - Intermediate B1

Germany: Upper-Intermediate B2

• Ukrainian: Native

Russian: Proficiency

### **Soft Skills**

- Self-motivation
- Responsibility
- Multitasking
- Flexibility
- Time Management
- Teamwork

#### CV online



#### Portfolio



# Internship

#### O November 2023 - December 2023

SoftRyzen | Kyiv, Ukraine (remote)

#### **Frontend Developer**

- Participated in the development of a website for a professional teeth whitening studio in Lviv (SmileBar)
- Developed the "Advantages" and "FAQ" sections with tab functionality
- Designed visual elements, including backgrounds, animations, and metadata integration
- Configured style variables in the tailwind.config file
- Studied documentation for Sanity and Telegram Bot API to understand their integration in the project
- Collaborated with the team to resolve cross-browser issues, using various libraries to optimize tabs and backgrounds
- Worked within an Agile team, utilizing Figma for design and Trello for task management

#### Oktober 2021 - December 2021

Legal Sector of the State Emergency Service of Ukraine | Kyiv, Ukraine

#### Lawyer

- Legal Sector of the State Emergency Service of Ukraine | Kyiv, Ukraine
- Practiced documentation management and compliance procedures during employee hiring and termination processes
- Reviewed and processed case materials, ensuring adherence to procedural standards
- · Conducted analytical work, including review and drafting of contracts and claims
- Collaborated with state systems for process tracking, gaining experience with data management and systemized workflows (e.g., €CITC, ACBΠ)

# **Experience**

#### Q July 2021 - August 2021

Ukrposhta I Ukraine, Kyiv

#### Leading specialist for the processing of objections

- Handling of complaints from individuals and legal persons
- Processing of requests from state and local authorities, law enforcement, judicial and regulatory authorities (use of Lotus Notes and the electronic document management system IT-Enterprise)
- Processing of lawyers' applications

#### April 2013 - July 2021

Ukrposhta I Ukraine, Kyiv

#### **Chief Specialist of the Postal Security Service**

- Creation, management and maintenance of a database of crimes committed by third parties (in Excel program)
- Analysis of data on offences in the field of postal communications
- Control of the results of the response of law enforcement and judicial authorities to reports of criminal offences in the company's field of activity
- Analysis of the results of the work of the security departments in the regions
- Preparation of crime reports and analytical certificates to the Ministry of Infrastructure of Ukraine